

SKILLS

- HTML & CSS
- JavaScript
- 🦊 jQuery & Ajax
- Vuejs & VueX
- Responsive Design
- **Bootstrap**
- UI & UX Practices
- Git & GitHub

CONTACT

- ★ Tapa House, Imam Dauda Street, Off Eric Moore, Surulere, Lagos.
- **L** +234 9033246067
- **1** +234 9052502653
- ✓ oladapodaniel10@gmail.com
- in in/oladapo-daniel-73a436172/
- f /olasunkanmioladapoayodeji
- Oladapodaniel

OLASUNKANMI OLADAPO DANIEL

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CAREER OBJECTIVES

A motivated frontend developer with 2+ years of experience in creating and developing dynamic, responsive web user interfaces. I have strong passion in developing excellent and engaging user interfaces and as someone who enjoys solving problems, software development was an obvious path.

Ready and qualified for the next stage in a successful career.

Currently looking for a suitable position with an ambitious company.

EXPERIENCE

Nov 2020 -Present

COMPLUS TECH LIMITED

Front-End Developer, Surulere Lagos Writing, designing and editing web page content, performing website updates as needed

Developing delightful user-facing features.

Identifying issues discovered by testing and feedback from internal and external clients, and correct problems.

Collaborating with teams on website plans, such as budgets, performance requirements, equipment or legal issues, including privacy and accessibility.

Apr 2020 -Oct 2020

CODE360

Front-end Developer (Trainee), Surulere Designed, built and maintained websites using the appropriate coding and scripting languages.

Turned UI/UX prototyped designs into creating excellent interactions from designs to development.

Wrote reusable code and libraries to a standard which makes it quick and easy to maintain the code in the future

Assisted the Development Manager to evaluate and improve software.

EDUCATION

2013 - 2016

B.A Philosophy

Olabisi Onabanjo University, Ago-Iwoye, Ogun

State

Second Class, Upper Division Hons.

CERTIFICATIONS & TRAININGS

Apr 2020 - FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT

Oct 2020 Code360, Surulere, Lagos.

An intensive front-end development training bootcamp which equips individuals with necessary skills to be a front-end developer.

Jan 2020 - **LEARN JAVASCRIPT AND JQUERY**

Apr 2020 Brad Traversy, Eduonix

An in-depth study of JavaScript and jQuery with

DOM manipulation.

Feb 2020 - **DIGITAL MARKETING**

Apr 2020 Google Digital Skills For Africa, Google

Google's structured course aimed at equipping individuals and business owners with digital marketing skills to increase sales and productivity

via the internet.

Feb 2018 GRADUATE LEADERSHIP AND MANAGEMENT

PRODUCTIVITY

Institute of Management, Productivity and Leader

ship Development, Gboko, Benue

Graduate Leadership and Management Professional (GLMP) Employability Skills and

Readiness.

PERSONAL TRAITS

- ✓ Has strong problem solving skills
- Excellent written and verbal communications skills
- Self motivated and self taught
- **Extremely organized and attentive to details.**
- **✓** Works without supervision and learns very fast.

REFEREES

Available on Request